Maurice Neufeld Additional Files /4230
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Maurice Neufeld Additional Files
1791-2005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Neufeld, Maurice F.
/4230
30 cubic feet
30 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8056634
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Casey Westerman, April 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Professor Maurice Frank Neufeld (October 27, 1910 -April 10, 2003) was an American academic, author, union organizer and Army officer. In 1945, he was one of the two founding faculty members of the School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, appointed by its founding dean, Irving Ives.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /4176: Maurice Neufeld Additional Papers /3007 AV: Maurice Neufeld "Grass Roots Founders and Grass Root Prodders: The Sources of Venture and Renewal for Democratic Education" Speech Audio-Visual Materials /4131m: Maurice Neufeld Additional Papers 5777: Maurice Neufeld Documents and Clipping Files /4229: Maurice Neufeld Additional Files 5515: Maurice F. Neufeld Collection of New York Times Clippings 5885: New York Times Additional Clipping File
Neufeld, Maurice F.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8056634
- Guide to correspondence and clippings; Correspondence: A Advisory. (Box 1)
  - Clipping and Correspondence, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Library of congress Neufeld Papers
  - Aa-A1 Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Am-AZ-Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Freedom, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ascoli Max, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ACTWU-- Rochester And Xerographic Division, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Asher Williams S, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administration ILR, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Administration ILR Meetings, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Council ILR, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Council ILR 2, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Council, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: American Anniversary. (Box 2)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Historians Organization, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ILR 50th Anniversary Volume, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Correspondence, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Anniversary 50th Correspondence book, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Correspondence 2, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Anniversary ILR 50 Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Anniversary 50th Kersey Miller Book, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Text First Drafts, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Text First Drafts 2, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Anniversary Text Book ILR First Drafts 3, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Anniversary. (Box 3)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Text First Drafts 4, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Texts Final Drafts 1, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Texts Final Drafts 2, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Texts Final Drafts 3, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Texts Final Drafts 4, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR MS sent to Francis Benson, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Texts Final copies 1, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Texts Final copies 2, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Texts Final Drafts reference reports, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Anniversary Coo. (Box 4)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Book Texts Introduction and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary 50th ILR Events, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Arbitration, meditation, Ombudsmen, Workplace "Courts"., 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Arts Architecture, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ba-Bd- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Bea-Bez Correspondence, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bf- Bn Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bo-Bt Correspondence, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bu-Bz Correspondence, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Ca-Ci Correspondence, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ck-Coo Correspondence, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Cop Cornell Faculty. (Box 5)
  - Cop- Cz Correspondence, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Cartoons, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Civil Liberties AVD Civil Rights, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining Meditation Arbitration, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Committee ILR, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Communication Press Radio Television Documentaries Computers, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Computer Information, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Conferences Meetings Seminars ILR, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Conferences Meetings Seminars-Outside, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Club of New York, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - CU Administration IV, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Administration Labor Relations, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Administration Labor Relations Clip, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University Colleges And Schools (general), 1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University Committee academic Freedom and Professional Statues, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Committees Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University Coms And Profs at Large, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University Coms Weiss Teaching Fellowship Award, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Cornell University CMS Willard Straight Takeover 20th, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cornell University Faculty, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University Faculty, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Cornell University History Clippings, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cornell University Faculty Meetings, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Correspondence: Cornell Libraries Development. (Box 6)
  - Cornell University Libraries April 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University Libraries Olin, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cornell University Libraries Olin User Committee, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University Libraries Users Committees April 1987, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cornell University Hearing Boards, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Courses ILR Graduate Cornell Baraugh Program, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Da-De Correspondence, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Df-Dm Correspondence, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dn-Dz Correspondence, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dean ILR Doherty, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - ILR Dean Lawler, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dean ILR Lipskey, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Defense Mobilization 2, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Development ILR, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Downey Thomas J, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: Downey Faculty. (Box 7)
  - Downey Thomas J, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Defense Mobilization And Demobilization, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Erickson Watt Charlotte Correspondence, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Early American Republic Society for Historians, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Economics, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Education, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Extension, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Fa-Fn Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fo-Fz Correspondence, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Faculty ILR Meetings, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Faculty Hd. (Box 8)
  - He-Hz Correspondence, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Faculty ILR Personnel Policy Appointments and Promotion, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Faculty ILR Personnel Policy Appointments and Promotion Lieberwitz, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Faculty ILR Legislation, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Films And Recordings, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Foundations Fellowships Grants, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ga-Gn Correspondence, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Go-Grh correspondence, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gri-Gz, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sarlock, Jonathan, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Government Public Administration Planning, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ha-Hd Correspondence 1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: He Italian Affairs. (Box 9)
  - He-Hz Correspondence, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Historical Studies, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Human Resources Personnel Management, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Human Resources Steering Committee ILR, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - ILR History, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - India, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Info and Materials Requirements Incoming, 1874 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Info and Materials Requirement Outgoing, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - ILR Review, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - International Exchange Of Persons, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - ISMS, 1818 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - International Affairs, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ives Irving M. Correspondence, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Correspondence: Italian Affairs Ld. (Box 10)
  - Joint Industry Board Electrical Industry NYC, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Judiciary, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - K Correspondence, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - J cooresponce, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kuwahara, Yasuo Correspondence, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Korman, A. Gerd, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - La-Ld Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: Le Library (ILR). (Box 11)
  - Library ILR, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Labor Political Action, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Labor Ownership (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Labor International, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Labor Developments 1, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Labor Developments 2, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Labor Developments 3, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Labor And Working Class History International, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Labor History Association, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Labor History (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Lj-Ly Correspondence, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Le-Li Correspondence, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Correspondence: Literature Personal. (Box 12)
  - Ma-Mc Correspondence, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Md-Mm Correspondece, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Mn-Mz Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - MAPS (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - MeikelJohn, Alexander, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Military Government, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Military History, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Minorities, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Music, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - N correspondence, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Neufield M.f, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: Personal. (Box 13)
  - Neufeld M.F. Personal-2, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Neufeld M.F. Personal 3, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Neufeld M.F. Personal 4, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Neufeld M.F. Personal Annual Report, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - MFN Personal Arbitration General, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - MFN Personal PUB EMP Disputes, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - MFN Personal AAA National Labor Panel, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - MFN Personal CIU Libraries, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - MFN Personal FMCS General, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - MFN Personal Early Laneer Clippinos, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Neufeld M.F. Personal FMCS, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - MFN Personal ILR LMDC, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Neufeld M.F. Personal Johnson Museum, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - MFN Personal National Mediation BD, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - MFN Personal Prisons, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - MFN Personal Travel, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Nut Mail, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - MFN Personal Xerox, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - MFN Personal Speaking Engagement, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Correspondence: Office Aides Rem. (Box 14)
  - Office Aides, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Office Correspondence, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Pa-Pe Correspondence, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - O Correspondence, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Pf- Pm Correspondence, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Pm-Pol Correspondence, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Poletti Charles, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Perkins, Frances, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Pom- Pz Correspondence, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Perry Lewis Correspondence, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Publications ILR, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Quotations Excerpts & Memorable Passages, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Ra-Ree Correspondence, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ref-Rm Correspondence, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Correspondence: Ro Sm. (Box 15)
  - Ro-Ros Correspondence, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Rot-Rz Correspondence, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Radicalism, Dissent (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Religion (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Research, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Research Associate, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Research Technician, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Research Club Of C.U, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Retirements ILR, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Saa-Saz Correspondence, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sea-Sez Correspondence, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Sb-Sd Correspondence, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sf-Sm Correspondence, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Correspondence: St Tz. (Box 16)
  - Stb-Sz Correspondence, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Sn-Sta Correspondence, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Salvatore Nicholas, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Science, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Social Conditions, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Speakers, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Staff, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - State New York Government 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - State University New York, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Statler Faculty Club, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Students ILR Alumni, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Student ILR Alumni, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Students ILR Applicants, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Student Applications Other schools 1, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Students General, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Students Graduate, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Student ILR Activities, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Student Services ILR, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Ta-Tg Correspondence, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Th-Tz Correspondence, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Correspondence: Travel World's Fairs. (Box 17)
  - Travel, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - U Correspondence, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - V Correspondence, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Wa-Wd Correspondence, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - We-Wh Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Wi-Wz Correspondence, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Wilson James, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Wilson James PHD, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Women, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Working Class History, 1880-1930 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - World Fairs, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Correspondence: World War II Z; Ph.D Thesis; Photographs; files from Prof. Neufeld's carrel in Olin Library:; Research Materials 1972-1983; Correspondence-Milton Konvitz 1995-1997; Correspondence-Jamie Silverstein 1997; Professor James A. Gross-Some Tho (Box 18)
  - ILR 50th Anniversary Volume, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Milton Konvitz, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Jaime silverstein 1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Professor James A. Gross, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Research Materials, 1972-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Neufeld PhD Thesis (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - The New York Times, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - The Contribution of the worlds Colombian Exposition, 1893 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Z correspondence, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Yugoslavian Affairs, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Y Correspondence, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Xerox, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - X Correspondence, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - World War 2, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Xerox Corporation Grievance Reports, ca. 1995-1998. (Box 19)
  - Xerox Grievances September 15, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Xerox Grievances August 29, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Xerox Grievances July 15, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Xerox Grievances April 05, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Xerox Grievances April 21, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Xerox Grievances May 9th, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Xerox Grievances May 22, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Xerox Grievances Jun 21, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Xerox Grievances March 21, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Xerox Grievances February 28, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Xerox Grievances Jan 25th, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Xerox Grievances Jan 15, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Xerox Grievances December 20, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Xerox Grievances December 06, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Xerox Grievances November 17th, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Xerox Grievances December 23, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Xerox Grievances December 28, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Xerox Grievances September 28, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Xerox Grievances February 29th, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Xerox Grievances June, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Xerox Grievances May 21, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Xerox Grievances May, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Xerox Grievances April 18th, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Xerox Grievances February 14th, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Xerox Grievances January 30th, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Xerox Grievances December18th, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Xerox Grievances November 29th, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Xerox Grievances Nov16, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Xerox Grievances April 11, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Xerox Grievances March 21, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Xerox Grievances March 11, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Xerox Grievances July 13th, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Xerox Grievances September 08 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Xerox Grievances May 1998 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Xerox Grievances March 14, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Xerox Grievances June 24, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Xerox Grievances August 26th, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Xerox Grievances November 2, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Xerox Grievances December 16, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Xerox Grievances February 19th, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Xerox Grievances December 17th, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Xerox Grievances Jan 29, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Xerox Grievances February 12, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Xerox Grievances March 16, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Xerox Grievances April 29, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Xerox Grievances April 01, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Xerox Grievances May 5, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Xerox Grievances May 20, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Xerox Grievances Jan 18, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Xerox Grievances July 21, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Xerox Grievances Nov 06, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Xerox Grievances September 15, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Xerox Grievances July 12, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Xerox Grievances September 10, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Xerox Grievances October 10, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Xerox Grievances November 08, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Xerox Grievances October 16th, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Xerox Grievances December 6, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Xerox Grievances Jan 14, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Xerox Grievances February 24, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Xerox Grievances March 19, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Xerox Grievances April 24, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 62)
- Articles; Fiction; Persistence. (Box 20)
  - Articles MFN Fiction Correspondence, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Articles MFN Founders Program, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Articles MFN Grass Roots Founders, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Articles MFN, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Articles MFN ILR Dawn Of the New Millennium, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H. Copyright, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Agreement, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Changes Appendix, 1879 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Changes bibliography, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Changes Footnotes, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Changes and explanations, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Changes Comm, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Changes Passages Quoted, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Changes Correspondence, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Articles MFN Italy L.H Trans IT Changes reprints, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Local 3 IBEW and Harry Van Arsdale Jr (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Articles MFN Perkins Tribute, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Articles MFN Perkins Tribute Reprints, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Articles MFN Persistence book, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Articles MFN Persistence books, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Articles MFN book Correspondence and criticism, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Articles MFN Persistence book, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Persistence; Poetry; Translations; Articles; Arts. (Box 21)
  - Articles Persistence book Ideas, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Articles MFN Persistence book the ideas sources (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Articles MFN Persistence Copies and Reprints, 1830 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Articles MFN Persistence Correspondence and Distribution, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Articles MFN Persistence Craftsmen role, 1830 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Articles MFN Persistence (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Articles MFN Persistence MS Versions (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Articles MFN Persistence Political Action Notes, 1834 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Arts MFN Persistence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Sources, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Poetry (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Poor Countries (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Realms, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Russia (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Arts MFN Persistence the sense of history (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Size of the Jacksonian Labor, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Size of the Jacksonian labor movement (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Size of the Jacksonian movement support=in data (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Arts MFN Persistence turner thesis (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Arts MFN Persistence vintage wine, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Arts MFN Persistence Wolfsan Tribute, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Persistence (4th revision), Articles (1927-1961). (Box 22)
  - Key to article books (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Arts MFN, 1927-1938 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Arts MFN, 1939-1945 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Arts MFN, 1946-1952 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Arts MFN, 1953-1960 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Arts MFN, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Articles (1929) and fiction. (Box 23)
  - Arts MFN Correspondence, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Arts MFN Antigone, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Arts MFN Bibliography American labor History, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Arts MFN American Labor History, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Arts MFN Book Rev, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Arts MFN experimental college, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Arts MFN failure AMG Italy, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Persistence sources, A-Kn. (Box 24)
  - Persistence Sources A-Ar, 1882 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Persistence Sources Ar, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Persistence Sources As-B, 1884 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Persistence Sources C-Cl 1, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Persistence Sources C-Cl 2, 1837 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Persistence Sources Co-D, 1835 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Persistence Source E-Ed (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Persistence Sources Ed 1, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Persistence Sources Ed 2- E1, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Persistence Sources Em-Ez, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Persistence Sources F (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Persistence Sources G (Box 24, Folder 12)